offerbox.com 2015-03-29

# The revolutionary online shopping assistant!

##### Privacy Policy and Cookies for OfferBox

1\. The Inclusion of Personal Data in AEDGE PERFORMANCE files:  
Pursuant to the provisions of Organic Law 15/1999 of 13 December pertaining to Personal Data Protection, all such information the User provides by means of this Website shall be collected and processed in files owned by AEDGE PERFORMANCE BCN, S.L.U (hereinafter referred to as “AEDGE PERFORMANCE”) to provide the services requested by the User, to respond to their requests and to keep the User informed of AEDGE PERFORMANCE’s products and services, including by way of electronic means.   
If you do not wish to receive such electronic information (emails), you may so indicate by ticking the boxes provided for that purpose, or by sending us an e-mail to legal@offerbox.com.The completion of all information marked as mandatory on this Website is necessary in order to ensure optimum provision of the services offered to the User. If this data is not provided, AEDGE PERFORMANCE does not guarantee that the information and services requested may be offered, correctly supplied or meet the needs of the User.  
AEDGE PERFORMANCE BCN, S.L.U. informs you that it has implemented the technical and organisational security measures deemed necessary to guarantee the security of your personal data and to prevent its alteration, loss, mishandling and/or unauthorised access thereto, in accordance with the status of technology, the nature of the data stored and the risks to which is exposed, whether from human action or physical or natural forces.

2\. Submission of data for staff selection:   
Curriculum Vitaes submitted by the User to AEDGE PERFORMANCE will be used for the sole purpose of responding to applications for employment related to jobs advertised. By providing your personal information, you acknowledge that the data provided is yours and is accurate and true. 

3\. Prohibition on registration by minors:   
Persons under the age of 14 must obtain prior consent from their parents or guardians before providing their personal information to AEDGE PERFORMANCE. If you are a minor, please ask your parents or guardians to contact us first. 

4\. Data Protection:  
By no means is personal data collected by OfferBox, and should any mention that OfferBox collects any type of personal data should be reputed as false.  
Personal data, which will consist only of Name and E-mail address, may be collected exclusively when the user submits a query through our online webform. Once the user has been given a satisfactory answer to the submitted query, the Personal data provided is removed.

5\. Exercise of rights:   
The User may exercise their rights to access, rectification, cancellation and opposition by sending an e-mail to [legal@offerbox.com](mailto:legal@offerbox.com "legal") or by writing to AEDGE PERFORMANCE, Avenida Diagonal 579, Planta 7ª, 08014, Barcelona. The User also has the right to submit a query or request through our online webform, or by sending an email to legal@offerbox.com, or by writing to AEDGE PERFORMANCE. The User also has the right to exercise the right to submit a query or request under TRUSTe's Trusted Download Program at https://tdp-feedback.truste.com/home.

6\. Communication of information by the User:   
Before providing personal information belonging to third parties, the User must obtain their prior express consent and inform the parties concerned of the terms of this privacy policy. The User shall indemnify and hold AEDGE PERFORMANCE harmless with regard to any possible claim, fine or penalty that it may be subject to arising from the User’s breach of the obligations set forth in this clause.

7\. Use of cookies:   
AEDGE PERFORMANCE may use cookies either directly or through third parties contracted for the provision of measurement services when the User accesses the Website. Cookies are files sent to the browser from a web server to record the User’s activities on the portal. The cookies used by the Website are solely associated with an anonymous user and their computer, and do not themselves provide any personal information regarding the User. Through the use of cookies, the server hosting the Website may recognise the browser used by the User in order to make web browsing simpler, for example by granting access for users who have previously registered to areas, services, promotions or competitions reserved exclusively for users without having to register every time they visit the Website. Cookies are also used to measure website audience and traffic parameters and to monitor the progress and number of visits. The User can also change the settings on their browser in order to receive notification of the receipt of cookies and to prevent the installation of cookies on their hard drive. Please refer to your web browser’s instructions and manuals for further information. To use this Website, the user does not have to allow the installation of cookies sent by the Website or third parties acting on behalf of AEDGE PERFORMANCE; however, the User may have to log in each time for those services requiring previous registration or “login”.

8\. OfferBox cookies:   
By using the OfferBox application, the user acknowledges and accepts that the software may install cookies from the companies Exelate UK Ltd., Criteo, Blue Kai, Inc. or AEDGE PERFOMANCE BCN, S.L.U. OfferBox does not use or has any access to the cookies from Exelate UK Ltd, Blue Kai, Inc. or Criteo. The user is able to configure their browser to not to accept cookies. More information regarding the use of cookies is available at [ http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ ](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). The Exelate UK Ltd privacy policy is available at [ http://exelate.com/new/consumer-privacy/website-privacy-policy/](http://exelate.com/new/consumer-privacy/website-privacy-policy/); the Criteo privacy policy: [ http://www.criteo.com/us/privacy-policy](http://www.criteo.com/us/privacy-policy), ; the Blue Kai privacy policy: <http://www.bluekai.com/privacypolicy.php> and that of AEDGE PERFROMANCE BCN, S.L.U. is available at [ http://www.aedgency.com/legal/privacy-policy/](http://www.aedgency.com/legal/privacy-policy/).

The OfferBox application can share data regarding the Internet web searches performed by the user and socio-demographic data with the company Criteo. Personal data is not at any time processed or transferred. For more information, the user can visit the Criteo Privacy Policy at at: <http://www.criteo.com/us/privacy-policy>.”

9\. OfferBox Proxy Server:  
Provided that the OfferBox application has been installed with the user’s prior consent, the software will use a proxy developed by AEDGE PERFORMANCE, which will intermediate between the Internet browser the user opts to browse the Internet and OfferBox. This intermediary software is used in a dissociated manner to the personal information in order to adapt the offers.
